ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files /4283/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series D: USWA Copper and Brass
  - History Information (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - OAB - Contracts (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - American Brass Materials (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Copper and Brass Bibliography (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Local 593 Material for Manual (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Photograph, charts
  - Local 593 Material for Manual (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Local 593 Material for Manual (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Introduction (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - The World Economy (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Dimensions of Competitiveness (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - History of Outokumpu American Brass (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - History of Local 593 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Steel Industry Case Study (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Auto Industry Case Study (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - The Brass and Copper Industry (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Diagram
  - Labor Relation Trends (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Strategies (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - OAB - 593 - Current Fall 1991 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - American Brass - Articles (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Outokumpu Articles (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - The Outokumpu Copper Group (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Inside Out (Outokumpu Magazine) (Box 12, Folder 27)
    3 - No.4/1990 issues & 1 - No.4/1990 issue
  - American Brass - Time Line (Box 12, Folder 28)
    Photocopy of an informational pamphlet
  - American Brass - Outokumpu Purchase (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - The Copper Courier (OAB Magazine) (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Mueller Industries (Box 12, Folder 31)
    1990 Annual Report
  - PMX & Poongsan Industries (Box 12, Folder 32)
    Newspaper
  - Resources (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - "The Competitive Advantage of Nations" (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - American Brass Resources (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Masters and Background Info. (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Vision in Progress (Folder 1 of 2), 1997 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Vision in Progress (Folder 2 of 2), 1997 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Finland: Information and Maps (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - International Copper Research Association, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 40)
    1989 Annual Report
  - Copper, Brass, Bronze Publications (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Copper. Brass, Bronze Annual Data, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - ASTM Standardization News (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - The Flow of Copper to U.S. Markets (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Background Information for Masters - John Hurst's Information (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Standard & Poor's Industry Surveys (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Dun & Bradstreet Million Dollar Directory 1960 & 1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Industrial Outlook (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Metals Handbook Tenth Edition, Vol. 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Cedar Rapids, Iowa Chamber of Commerce, Econ. Development (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Cedar Rapids Information (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - CRB Commodity Year Book, 1956-1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Trade Zone Info. and PMX (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - World Mineral Statistics (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Poster
  - Bureau of the Census Info. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Metal Statistics, 1957-1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Metal Statistics, 1972-1977 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Metal Statistics, 1981-1990 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Articles and Tables of Information (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Growth Patterns in Copper Consumption in Industrializing Countries (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Assessing the U.S. Automotive Radiator Market's Demand for Copper/Brass (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Assessing the Air Conditioning Market's Demand for Copper Tube (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - General Copper & Brass Articles (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Cites for Articles, Book and Papers (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - John Hurst: Phone Interviews (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Nonferrous Metals: Industry Structure (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - The Global Copper Industry: Problems and Prospects (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Michigan Copperland - Boston Dollars (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Brass Valley (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Mine Mill (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Copper: Technology & Competitiveness OTA - E - 367 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - AB - 593 - Adm. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Co. & Union Artwork (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Lexis Nexis: American Brass, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - OAB - LU 593 (Folder 1 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 29)
    Charts
  - OAB - LU 593 (Folder 2 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Human Resource Guide
  - OAB - LU 593 (Folder 3 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - OAB - LU 593 (Folder 4 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 32)
    Finnish Outokumpu Company Magazine
  - OAB - LU 593 (Folder 5 of 5) (Box 13, Folder 33)
    Survival Guide to the Stress of Organizational Change; Education Program Proposal
  - OAB - 593 Survey, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - OAB - LU 593 Industrial Education, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - OAB - LU 593 Current (Folder 1 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - OAB - LU 593 Current (Folder 2 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - OAB - LU 593 Current (Folder 3 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Charts; Agenda
  - Local 593 Handouts (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - OAB Grants (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Brass - Overview (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - International Trade Commission of U.S. Report on Brass Imports (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - It's You Business - Follow Up (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Series E: Telecommunications
  - Telecommunication, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Jan Pierce (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Jeff Keefe (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - AT & T (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Jim Dowdall - NYNEX (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Telecommunications Consortium - Harry Katz (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Telecommunication - Current (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Telecommunications Exchange (Folder 1 of 2), 1993 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    NYFACT Folder
  - Telecommunications Exchange (Folder 2 of 2), 1993 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Telecommunications - ICC (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Telecommunications Transformation Implications for Work and Employment, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Meeting Material April 7, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Meeting Materials April 26, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Meeting Materials May 21, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Meeting Materials May 26, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Meeting Materials September 13, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Meeting Materials November 16, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - The Report of the Governor's Telecommunications Exchange First Draft October 15, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Connecting to the Future the Report of the Telecommunications Exchange November 11, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Telecommunications Exchange Report Draft November 24, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Telecommunications Exhange Report Draft December 10, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Telecommunication Study, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Telecommunication Industry (Box 14, Folder 33)
    Multiple telephone Company Folders
  - CWA District 1 Telecommunications Forum, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Rosemary Batt Papers, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Government Minority Ownership Regulations in an Era of Converging Technology, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - The Governor's Telecommunication Conference June 16-17,1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunication Workers (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - New York State Economic Development Plan, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - CWA - Bell South, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Michael G. McGlynn Papers, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Unionization Rates, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Chairman's Information Seminar on Telecommunications Technology January 29,1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Work Force, Labor and Training Issues (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Employment Trends in Telecommunications: The National View (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Telecommunication Articles (Folder 1 of 7) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Telecommunication Articles (Folder 2 of 7) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Telecommunication Articles (Folder 3 of 7) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Telecommunication Articles (Folder 4 of 7) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Telecommunication Articles (Folder 5 of 7) (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Chart
  - Telecommunication Articles (Folder 6 of 7) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Telecommunication Articles (Folder 7 of 7) (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Erik Stein, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Series F: Arts and Entertainment
  - Arts and Entertainment (Folder 1 of 6) (Box 15, Folder 18)
    ILR Arts Informational Folder
  - Arts and Entertainment (Folder 2 of 6) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Arts and Entertainment (Folder 3 of 6) (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Playbill; Cansius College Magazine; Binational Tourism Informational Folder
  - Arts and Entertainment (Folder 4 of 6) (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Urbanomics; AEO 2007 National Conference
  - Arts and Entertainment (Folder 5 of 6) (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Arts and Entertainment (Folder 6 of 6) (Box 15, Folder 23)
    October issue of Buffalo Spree; Multiple information packets
  - Meeting Materials June 19, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Pictures, Report
  - A & E Film Study (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Playbill, charts and figures
  - A & E Projects December 2008 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Geography of Artists in Business: Notes and Draft (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Distribution maps
  - Visual Arts Project (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Hallwalls (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Hallwalls Capital Campaign
  - AFL - CIO A & E (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Upstate Arts Organization (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - A & E Mark Jones (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Arts and Entertainment Advisory Committee Notes, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Photograph
  - Scott Behrend Theatre July 2006 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Arts and Entertainment Industry Project, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Sloan Foundation (Folder 1 of 8), 2004-2008 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Issue of Cornell Chronicle Magazine
  - Sloan Foundation (Folder 2 of 8), 2004-2008 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Sloan Foundation (Folder 3 of 8), 2004-2008 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Sloan Foundation (Folder 4 of 8), 2004-2008 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Conference Agenda; Humanities issue of Cornell Chronicle
  - Sloan Foundation (Folder 5 of 8), 2004-2008 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Sloan Foundation (Folder 6 of 8), 2004-2008 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Sloan Foundation (Folder 7 of 8), 2004-2008 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    January issue of The Economist.
  - Sloan Foundation (Folder 8 of 8), 2004-2008 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Sloan Foundation Report (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Above Ground: Information on Artist III Executive Summary, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Artists' Centers: Evaluation and Impact on Careers, Neighborhoods and Economics, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Artography: Arts in a Changing America, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Arts and Economic Prosperity: The Economic Impact of Nonprofit Arts Organizations and Their Audiences, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Arts as an Industry, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    Two copies
  - Close-Up: The Geography of Artists in Greater Buffalo, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - The Creative Economy Practitioner's Toolkit: Taking Advantage of Campus and Community Resources, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Creative Economy Strategies For Small and Medium Size Cities: Options for New York State, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Creative New York, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Center for an Urban Future Report
  - Crossover: How Artists Build Careers across Commercial, Nonprofit and Community Work, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Cultural Capital: Challenge's to New York State's Competitive Advantages in the Arts and Entertainment Industry, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Cultural Capital Early Drafts, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    2 Copies
  - Cultural Diplomacy and the National Interest (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Cultural Tourism in The Buffalo-Niagara Region, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - The Economic Impact of Travel & Tourism in New York State, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Presentation with various charts and graphs
  - Empire State Commercial Production Credit, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Application and forms
  - Empire State's Cultural Capital at Risk? Key Findings, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    3 copies
  - Empire State's Cultural Capital at Risk?, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    2 copies containing charts and maps
  - Empire State's Cultural Capital At Risk? Drafts, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - How the United States Funds the Arts, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Taking Hold of the New Economy, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Institutional Barriers to Recruitment and Employment in the Audio Visual Industries, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    The Effect on Black and Minority Ethnic Workers
  - Measuring the Economic and Social Impact of the Arts: A Review (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - NYC Economic Impact Strategy for the Arts, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Request for Proposals
  - New York State as a Global Competitive Hub: A Competitive Analysis of Four Theories on World Cities, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - New York's Big Picture, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - New York's Big Picture Conference Packets January 15, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    3 Copies
  - Research on Selected Sectors of the Arts, Media and Entertainment Industry, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Sonic City: The Evolving Economic Geography of the Music Industry, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Urban Development and the Politics of a Creative Class: Evidence from the Study of Artists, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Working in the Creative Economy: Assessing the Needs and Opportunities in WNY, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Series G: Workplace, Industry and Economic Development (WIED)
  - Highlights Report, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Current Regional Adm., 2002 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - WR Faculty July 2002 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    Meeting Agenda
  - Economist Search, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Funding, 2002-2006 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - EDI, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    Flyer
  - EDI Planning, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - WNY Sustainable Energy, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Western New York Foundation Grant, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Community Foundation Grant, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - EDI - 2004 - Incl. Funding (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - EDI - 2005 State Funding (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - WIED Team Meeting October 27, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Other Cornell Resources, 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - WIED People, 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Presentations
  - WIED Administration (Folder 1 of 2), 2005-2009 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - WIED Administration (Folder 2 of 2), 2005-2009 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Immigrant Projects, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - ILR - Spitzer - Public Sector, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - ILR - R & R July 2006 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - CNY Projects, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - WIED, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - WIED- Buffalo June 20, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - WIED - E - SCANS, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - WIED - Ithaca May 8-9, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    WIED Environmental Scan Overview
  - WIED Restructuring, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - WIED - State Funding, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Partnership for Energy Innovation, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Workforce Development Environmental Trends Scan, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - WIED - Adm. & Projects, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - WIED General (Folder 1 of 5), 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    National Grid Agenda
  - WIED General (Folder 2 of 5), 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - WIED General (Folder 3 of 5), 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    Conference Report
  - WIED General (Folder 4 of 5), 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - WIED General (Folder 5 of 5), 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - WIED Plans, 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - WIED Administrative Support, 2006-2008 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - WIED Highlights, 2006-2008 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Buffalo State Collaboration, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - FRB - ILR Workforce, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Workforce Meeting Agenda
  - Reggie, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Issue of USW At Work
  - Russell Sage Foundation Grant, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Workforce, Industry and Economic Development Leadership Retreat February 2 - 3, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Syracuse March, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Preliminary Report to NYSAC
  - Lou Jean - Syracuse March 22 - 23, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - WIED May 15-16, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - WIED Fall 2007 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - WIED, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Wind Action - Daemen, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Workforce Literacy Summit, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Reggie - Child Care, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Central New York Labor-Management Assessment Summary Report
  - WIED Faculty Goals, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - WIED - General, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Yael, 2007-2009 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Women in the Knowledge Economy Presentation
  - Art, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Child Care - Mildred W., 2008 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - General ILR Transitions, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Jeff - Youth Apprenticeship, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Power Building in California Draft Report; Community Values Toolkit Presentation
  - Maria & Lois, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - WIED Spring 2008 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - WIED March 2008 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Goal Setting (Folder 1 of 2), 2008-2009 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Goal Setting (Folder 2 of 2), 2008-2009 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Maralyn, 2008-2009 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    2008 Report on the Commute Challenges Faced in Onondaga County
  - WIED Budgets, 2008-2009 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - WIED Transitions, 2008-2009 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - WIED Accounts, 2000-2009 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - EDG, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Buffalo Niagara JOBS Initiative Meeting and Meeting Report
  - Instructor Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Champions at Work (Folder 1 or 2), 2004-2006 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Champions at Work (Folder 2 or 2), 2004-2006 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Academic Job Search Sample, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Mining Hidden Assets, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    The Apollo Project; Mining Hidden Assets Presentation
  - Non - Academic Staff Job Search Sample, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Workshops for Professional Development Booklet
  - "Partners for Progress", 2005 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Economic Development General (Folder 1 of 3), 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Transitioning to a Sustainable World Presentation
  - Economic Development General (Folder 2 of 3), 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Economic Development General (Folder 3 of 3), 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Issues 3 and 4 of the Buffalo Economy Tracker
  - Erie County Study, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    ECCC Roundtable and Community Forum
  - Institute for Workforce Studies, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Central NY Economic Development (Folder 1 of 2), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Workforce New York Informational Packet
  - Central NY Economic Development (Folder 2 of 2), 2006 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Buffalo Child Care Means Business Presentation
  - Connecting Regional Businesses With Cornell Resources, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Diversity and Inclusion, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Thematic Group on Conflict & Labor Relation Presentation Note Slides
  - Employee Assistance Program (EAP) Sample, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Expo, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    2 copies
  - Hottest Place to be Cool, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Business & Labor at Work Informational Folders
  - ILR Organizational Change Group, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - ILR Outreach and Extension Planning, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Institute for Women and Work, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Living Wages, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Retreats, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Syracuse E.D. - O.F.D.C.U., 2006 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - WIED, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - WIED November 2006 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Buffalo Child Care, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Expo, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    Higher Education Within an Integrated Economic Development Strategy Presentation
  - Lead Meeting January 2007 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    Disability, Workplace & Employment Support Practice Catalog
  - Lead Meeting & Phone Meeting June & August 2007 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    EDI Annual Report
  - Thematic Leads March 2007 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Bruce Newman, 2009-2010 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    Labor Management
  - FRBNY Econ. Forum, 2009-2010 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    The Higher Education Industry and the Stock of Local Human Capital
  - Believe in Buffalo - Niagara (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - WIED Sloan Finance (Box 20.1, Folder 1)
  - WIED EDA February - June 2007 (Box 20.1, Folder 2)
  - WIED ESD (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 20.1, Folder 3)
  - WIED ESD (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 20.1, Folder 4)
- Series H: Champions at Work Study
  - Champions at Work Executive Summary, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Champions at Work Distribution, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Buffalo Niagara Enterprise, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Town of Tonawanda Development Corp., 2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Western New York Economic Survey (Folder 1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Western New York Economic Survey (Folder 2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Buffalo News Articles on Strikes (Folder 1 of 2), 1993-2000 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Buffalo News Articles on Strikes (Folder 2 of 2), 1993-2000 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Pertinent Statistical Data, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Champions at Work - Press Stuff, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Progress and Request, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Champions Survey Data, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Codebooks: Wester New York Union Employers (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Champions: Quotes from Surveys (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Champions: Bibliographic Work (Martin's) (Folder 1 of 3), 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Champions: Bibliographic Work (Martin's) (Folder 2 of 3), 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Champions: Bibliographic Work (Martin's) (Folder 3 of 3), 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Champions: Economic Research (Folder 1 of 2), 2000 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Champions: Economic Research (Folder 2 of 2), 2000 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - American Axle Interviews, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra Interviews, 1993-1999 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Catholic Health System Interviews, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Empire Specialty Steel Interviews, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - General Mills Interviews, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - GM Power Train Interviews, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Honeywell Interviews, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Kaleida Health Interviews, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Kaleida Health Information Folder
  - Moog Interviews, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Motorola, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - NFTA Interviews, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Outokumpu American Brass Interviews, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Project Labor Agreements Interviews, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Quebecor World Interviews, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Sysco Interviews, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Tops Interviews, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Trico Products, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - IBEW Interviews, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Champions Articles and News Coverage, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Other Information (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Press, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Champions: Labor Focus Group, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Article Summary or the "Champion at Work" Study (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Series I: Regional Economic Development
  - Labor Market Study (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Labor Market Assessment (Folder 1 of 2), 2010 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Labor Market Assessment (Folder 2 of 2), 2010 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    Buffalo Niagara Labor Market Presentation
  - Labor Market Assessment Articles, 2007-2010 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    N.L.R.B. Election Report
  - University of Buffalo Regional Institute, 2009-2010 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Labor Relations Information, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Buffalo Niagara Enterprise Request for Proposal, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Buffalo Employment and Training Center Information Packet (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Champions Research March 2003 (Box 23, Folder 1)